Katarzyna Niedziela

13 Conmere Square, M15 6DE Manchester ka.niedziel@gmail.com Mobile: 077368 03222

I am an openminded history and journalism graduate with the soul of an artist. I play flute and love music; I enjoy drawing, painting and I am interested in visual arts and design. Whilst living in Poland I've worked in a newspaper writing articles. I enjoyed writing since I remember and I hope that one day I will write a book. I am always looking towards improving myself and consider myself an ambitious and hardworking person, agile and quick to pick up new skills.

Work Experience

July- December 2016 (UK): PA of Managing Director in Financial Brokers Ltd

Personal assistant

I was the first point of contact for the employees and customers. I was also supporting the work of managing Directors: arranging business meetings and greeting clients in the office, organising office supplies, taking phone calls. I helped to organise business trips, I was responsible for booking hotels, plane tickets, restaurants, renting cars. I undertook many tasks requiring research, decision-making process, self-reliance.

Office admin

I was responsible for making and receiving payments from clients, creating invoices, managing company's bank accounts. I've also kept company's expenses sheet up to date. I was in charge of counting employees commissions and preparing salary invoices. I was also keeping record of employees holiday days. I was responsible for sorting the mail and handing it to the right persons.

January- June 2016 (UK): Burnus Company Ltd

Advertising

Used my experience and skills as journalist to get the company better recognized. I've directed and edited a promo commercial which yielded an increase in purchases. Designed and wrote the content of leaflets and brochures that attracted new customers. Edited and kept the website content up to date. Brought the company into social media by creating and running Facebook and Instagram accounts. Promoted the company at UK's Concrete Show 2016 where I've talked with various onlookers and raised awareness of the company's products.

Sales & International Deliveries

In charge of running the Amazon and Ebay accounts- I was responsible for product listings, setting up promotions, arranging deliveries. I was also a facilitator for international clients on handling shipping of raw materials. Arranged collections and deliveries of transports going to/from our warehouse. Responsible for tending to all the details needed and making sure that transports were on time.

Front Desk Office

Arranged meetings with clients, handled phone calls and emails. Kept the office tidy, organised the paperwork and formatted electronic documents and files.

June- August 2014 (Poland): Customer Advisor

Worked as a customer consultant in the Open Finance call centre. Dealt with financial issues such as credits, bonds and stocks. As a seller I learned how to persuade customers, build trust in our products and how to discuss customer's problems. Handled client complaints in a calm, peaceful way. Working in a team taught me how to cooperate with other people and function as a group, not only as a lone seller.

2013-2014 (Poland): Newspaper Reporter

During college I worked as a journalist in a widely known polish daily newspaper - Gazeta Wyborcza. I was writing paper issues as well as website articles. I was searching for new stories, taking interviews, doing researches, and in the end, cooperating with editorial office, to close the issue.

Many a times I was working under pressure and coping with tight deadlines. This taught me how to better organize and prioritize my time.

Other Experience

2015-2016	Sandwich artist in Subway (UK) Working in customer service, I learned to keep and follow food procedures, I was also running the shop by myself during morning shifts.
2014	Radio Reporter in Zlote Przeboje Radio- internship (Poland)
2013	Tv reporter in TVP Lublin -internship (Poland)
2012	Archivist in Institute of National Remembrance -internship (Poland)
2011	Child Animator on Toyota's playground -summer job (Poland)
2009	Waiter in Ramzes Restaurant (Poland)
Education	
2011-2014	University of Marie Curie-Skłodowska, Lublin, Poland

2011-2014	University of Marie Curie-Skłodowska, Lublin, Poland BSc Journalism, Specialisation: Media
2011-2013	University of Marie Curie-Skłodowska, Lublin, Poland MSc History, Specialisation: Archivist; Secondary: Media in the past
2008-2011	University of Marie Curie-Skłodowska, Lublin, Poland BSc History, Specialisation: Archivist
2005-2008	High School no. 1, Zamość, Poland
2001-2011	Music School, Zamość; Music School Lublin, Poland Music Diploma, Main instrument: flute; additional instrument: piano

Skills and Abilities

Computer literate: Windows, Microsoft Office package (Excel, Powerpoint, Word), Photoshop, Pinnacle Studio (film edition).

Languages: Polish - native, English- advanced.

Interest and Hobbies

Playing music, salsa dancing, drawing and painting, reading books.